獸醫剛來電話
The vet called.
斯黛拉的體檢結果出來了
Stella's test results came back.
他想讓我把她帶回去... 今天
He wants me to bring her in...today.
不 過來抱一下
Oh, no. Come here, you.
杰 我很遺憾
Oh, Jay, I'm so sorry.
但這就是喜歡寵物的壞處 對吧
That is the bad thing about loving animals, right?
但是想想你帶給她了多少美好的事情
But think about all the wonderful things you gave her,
像是美麗的家 美味的食物...
like a beautiful home, delicious food...
...還有我們的婚床
...our marital bed.
節哀順變 我們會將她銘記于心的
I'm sorry, Jay. Stella will not be forgotten.
我不是要帶她去安樂死 你個女巫
I'm not putting her down, you goblin.
她需要做手術
She needs a surgery.
那真是個好消息
Oh. That is such great news.
斯黛拉怎么了
Oh, what's wrong with Stella?
她患有軟腭過長癥
She has an elongated soft palate,
所以有時候會難以呼吸
which is why sometimes it's hard for her to breathe.
并且睡覺打呼嚕
And she snores a lot.
那他們能給你也做這手術嗎
Any chance that they can do you, too?
這是個嚴肅的手術 他們得對她進行全身麻醉
This is a serious operation. They have to put her out.
如果她醒不過來怎么辦
What happens if she doesn't wake up?
我要怎么辦
What would I do?!
我去拔智齒的時候
When I got my wisdom teeth out,
你為了在十點半的截止時間前買到雞蛋麥芬
you made me walk the last four blocks to the dentist
讓我走了最后的四個街區去到牙醫那里
so you could get an Egg McMuffin before the 10:30 cut-off.
你得把這事兒忘了
You're gonna have to let that go.
你知道嗎 我不會做的
You know what? I'm not gonna do it.
-她看起來很好 -也許她只是需要
- She seems fine. - Maybe she just needs
一些新鮮空氣來保證呼吸順暢
some fresh air to breathe better.
我們何不帶她去狗狗公園呢
Why don't we take her to the dog park?
這是個好主意 不過外面可能有點泥濘
That's a great idea. Might be a little muddy out there.
我去拿你的靴子 美女
I'm gonna get your boots, gorgeous.
謝謝你
Thank you.
我的靴子在壁櫥里 就在...
My boots are in the closet, next to the --
他剛才是在對斯黛拉說話嗎
Was he just talking to Stella?
過來抱一下
Come here, you.
皇冠造型護墻板 皇冠造型護墻板
Crown molding wainscoting, crown molding wainscoting,
法式門信用評分 法式門信用評分
French door credit score, French door credit score.
在為重要的房屋展示做熱身嗎
You warming up for a big showing?
非常重大
Very big.
我終于給胡嬌找到了他的夢之屋
I finally found Pepper his dream house.
我不敢相信你還在
I can't believe you're still
為那個男人浪費時間
letting that man waste your time.
你都給他看了多少房子了
How many houses have you shown him?
就只有... 我不知道 120棟嗎
Only, like -- I don't know, like, uh, 120.
但我們玩得很開心 他很有意思
But we have fun. He's a hoot.
親愛的 就連米奇和小卡都同意
Honey, even Mitch and Cam agree that he's impossible,
他不可能也不會買一棟房子
and he's never gonna buy a house.
-他會的 -不會的
- Yes, he will. - No.
他總能雞蛋里挑骨頭
He always manages to find something wrong.
上一棟房子 瑜伽間離安全室太近了
The last house, the yoga room was too close to the panic room.
他本來是愿意接受的
He was willing to live with that,
但那塊地不適合他養的獵鷹
but the property wasn't zoned for his falcons.
不過今天的這棟 符合他期望清單的每一條
This one today, though, checks every single box.
很好 那么如果胡嬌今天沒買下房子
Great. So if Pepper doesn't buy the house today,
你得答應別讓他再纏著你了
you agree to stop letting him string you along
你得放棄他這個客戶
and drop him as a client.
咱倆達成交易之前 你纏了我多久
How long did you string me along before I closed that deal?
親愛的 你沒法讓胡嬌懷孕
Honey, you can't get Pepper pregnant
-并且把他困在一個房子里 -我們走著瞧
- and trap him in a house. - You're on.
你記得要在五點到家吧
You remember you need to be home
-對吧 -記得
- at five, right? - Yeah.
等等 為什么
Wait, why?
艾麗克斯的男朋友 比爾 搞了一些發明
Alex's boyfriend, Bill, has cooked up some invention
想讓我們投資
he wants us to invest in.
為什么是我們呢
Why us?
因為有人給了他鼓舞了他
Because someone inspired him.
你們可以看到 我正在審查中的專利
As you can see, my patent-pending
穿戴式椅子 穿戴不會有累贅感
Wear-Chair TM, barely noticeable.
-我喜歡 -不管何時我站累了
- I love it. - Whenever I get tired of standing,
我只需要 按下這個按鈕
all I have to do -- press this button.
一條彈簧腿就會噴射出來 提供舒適的座位
A spring-loaded leg jets out to provide me with a comfy seat.
你把它穿反了 是嗎
You put it on backwards, didn't you?
我想說的是 比爾
My point is, Bill,
我們每個人內心都有一項偉大的發明
there's a great invention inside all of us.
拜托了 準時到家就行
Please, just be home in time.
我可不想獨自打破一個男人的夢想
I don't want to crush a man's dreams on my own.
你得跟我一起
You have to do it with me.
誰知道呢 也許我們會喜歡他的發明
Who knows? We might love his invention.
肯定會很傻的
It's gonna be stupid.
幸好你沒和喬治·福爾曼結婚
Good thing you weren't married to George Foreman
否則我們現在還是一次只能烤一面肉
or we'd still be grilling our meats one side at a time.
莉莉 你 你今天怎么樣啊
So, Lily, how -- how are you today?!
莉莉
Lily?!
Lily.
你爸爸剛才問你今天過得如何
Your father was just asking how you're doing.
你還好嗎
Are -- Are you all right?
-我很好 -好的
- I'm fine. - Okay.
好
Yeah.
我剛才給你打手勢
Okay, uh... I gestured you over here
是因為我們得討論一下莉莉的事
'cause we need to talk about Lily.
我推理出來了
Yes, I puzzled that out.
而且 你也不需要小聲說話 看著
Also, you don't need to whisper. Watch.
親愛的 你爸爸和我可能要離婚了
Honey, your father and I may get divorced
因為他正考慮變性成個女人
because he's thinking about becoming a woman.
這解釋了很多事情
That explains a lot.
-我在兩首歌的間隙 -夠了 出來 這邊
- I'm in between songs. - Okay, all right. Now out. This way.
她到底怎么了
What is going on with her?
我不想再被關在她心門外了
I don't want to be shut out like this another day.
我知道 但我們 我們先別驚慌失措吧
I know, but let's -- let's not get hysterical.
我才沒有驚慌失措
I'm not getting hysterical.
-你也就能再撐幾分鐘 -的確
- We're minutes away. - Fair enough.
我只是想看她笑
I just want to see her smile.
好的 我要給羅納多再發個短信
Yeah, okay, I'm gonna text Ronaldo again.
希望他能讓我們參加吉米的愛派對
Hopefully he got us into that KimmyLoveandStuff party.
吉米的愛是一個莉莉喜歡的
KimmyLoveandStuff is an Internet sensation
-網絡紅人 -沒錯
- that Lily loves. - Yeah.
她試穿衣服
She tries on clothes,
她哭訴霸凌和塑料
she cries about bullies and plastic.
大伙兒 想象一下
You guys, just imagine
你是一只海龜 這事兒發生在你身上
if you were a turtle and this happened to you.
我們全家都為她著迷
Our whole family is obsessed with her.
這就是一個少女
And that's the great thing about a tween girl
有兩個同志爸爸的好處
having two gay dads.
我是說 我們 我們愛好一致
I mean, we -- we love the same things.
小鮮肉 時尚 八卦
Cute guys, fashion, gossip.
我的天哪 羅納多 他把我們弄進去了
Oh, my God! Ronaldo, he got us in!
了不起
Amazing.
我們得給他一個感謝禮物
Okay, we have to get him a thank-you gift.
不 不 他欠你的 好嗎
No, no, he owes you, okay?
你給了他你的骨髓
You gave him your bone marrow.
我怎能不給呢
Well, how could I not?
他沒吃飽 我又一點都吃不下了
He was still hungry, and I wasn't gonna eat any more of it.
然后我們回到正式的入口
And we make our way back to the formal entryway,
根據你的期望清單
which, according to your checklist,
"要大到當人們進入的時候
"Must be large enough to make people swoon
就會為此傾倒"
when they step inside."
我想再來一遍
I want to do it again.
那個胡嬌自稱很有錢
Ugh, that Pepper claims to be wealthy,
我才不信...
but I don't believe it for a --
我的天哪
Oh, my heavens!
我們就是鄉巴佬
We're peasants.
這里的一切都符合你的期望...
It's got everything on your list --
鋼琴吧 他和他的餐廳
piano bar, his and his dining rooms,
還要能看到蕾哈娜的屋頂 這點我一直沒懂
plus a view of Rihanna's roof, which I never quite understood.
我給她辦過一次派對 我能感覺
I did a party for her once, and I could feel
那雙巴貝多人的眼睛用看不上的眼神俯視了我
those judgy Barbadian eyes looking down on me.
現在誰在俯視著誰呢 日日
Now who's looking down on who, RiRi?
常言道 地點 地點 復仇
Like they say, location, location, vengeance.
你真有意思
You're funny.
這房子太好了 菲爾 媽媽會喜歡的
Oh, it's fabulous, Phil. Mother would love it.
正是她的慷慨和我的委托
It's her generosity and my power of attorney
才讓購買這座房子成為可能
that are making this purchase possible.
所以 我們準備好簽報價單了嗎
So...are we ready to sign the offer?
就快了
Very close.
我還想在里面住一小會兒
I just want to live in it for a bit,
體驗一下日常生活的感覺
get a feel for the everyday.
你不著急 對吧
You're in no hurry, right?
不不不 要是我著急
Oh, no, no, no. If I was in a hurry,
怎么會帶你看了兩百多座房呢
would I have shown you over 200 houses?
我等不及要去公園了
I can't wait to get to the park.
那是我們的郵遞員
Hey, there's our mailman.
冷靜點 杰
Settle down, Jay.
天 我今天好癢
Boy, I'm itchy today.
我希望那只叫賓果的狗在公園
Hey, I hope that dog Bingo's at the park.
和他玩很有意思
He's fun to play with.
你在干什么 你錯過那個轉彎了
What are you doing? You just missed our turn.
我只是從另一條路走
I'm just going another way.
沒有別的路了
There is no other way.
你不是要帶我們去公園
You're not taking us to the park.
我們要去看獸醫
We're going to the vet.
醫生說了她需要做手術
The doctor said that she needs this surgery.
她會沒事的
She's gonna be fine.
我不舒服 我要透透氣
I feel sick. I need some air.
這里是我在新房子的普通的一天
So, here I am on an ordinary day in my new house
大家都嫉妒我 而我昂首闊步 洋洋得意
everyone hates me for and I'm walking and I'm kvelling...
我們氣喘吁吁 大汗淋漓
And we're panting and we're schvitzing...
我們笑 我們哭
And we're laughing and we're crying...
我們陷入思考
And we're thinking.
我在擊球
And I'm putting.
所以你的車里
So, you have an entire wardrobe
有一整個衣柜嗎
in your car?
? 我在演奏 我在歌唱 ?
♪ And I'm playing and I'm singing ♪
? 大家都愛死了 ?
♪ And they're loving it ♪
我說愛死了
I said loving it.
這簡直是場災難
This is a disaster!
真是"閃亮登場"啊
What a fun way to enter a room.
我知道今天比爾要來和你們聊聊
I know Bill's coming over to talk to you guys today,
-我要崩潰了 -寶貝 不用擔心
- and I'm freaking out. - Oh, honey, don't worry.
我們不會投資他的發明的
We're not gonna invest in his invention.
那不是他想和你們談話的原因
That's not why he wants to talk to you.
那是個幌子
It's a cover.
他要征求你們的祝愿娶我
He's going to ask for your blessing to marry me.
-什么 -你們不能同意
- Whoa, what? - And you have to tell him no.
你怎么知道的
How do you know this?
他們家所有男人都在情人節求婚
All of the men in his family propose on Valentine's Day,
情人節馬上就到了
which is coming up.
我看了他給剛訂婚的朋友
I read a text he sent to his buddy
發的短信 詢問一些關于
who just got engaged asking for tips
求婚順利的秘訣 而且我的朋友看見他
for a good proposal, and my friend saw him
從一家珠寶店出來
coming out of a jewelry store.
所以你翻他的短信還追蹤他的行蹤
So you read his texts and you track his movements.
這下我可知道他為什么這么想綁住你了
I can see why he's so eager to lock you down.
你看 我真的很喜歡和比爾在一起
Look, I really like being with Bill,
如果我不得不拒絕他
and if I have to turn him down,
那我們的感情就完了
that means the end of the relationship
美好的性愛也沒了
and all that great sex.
你現在可真是釋放真我啊 是吧
Really come out of your shell, haven't you?
好了 你準備好了嗎 驚喜
Okay. Are you ready?! Surprise!
我還需要點提示信息
I'm gonna need a little bit more information.
你現在在吉米的愛
You are at KimmyLoveandStuff's
新化妝品系列的
exclusive launch party...
獨家發布派對 她還要演唱
...for her new makeup line, and she's gonna sing
-她的熱門單曲 -單曲
-her hit single... - Single!
《給我愛》
..."Give Me Love and Stuff."
好吧 你們是怎么做到的
Okay. How did you guys do this?
你們好啊 陌生人 歡迎
Hello, total strangers. Welcome.
非常感謝你做的一切 羅納多
Thank you so much for doing this, Ronaldo.
要是有人問你們是誰
If anyone asks who you are,
就說你們在找加斯·布魯克斯[鄉村歌手]的簽售
say you were looking for the Garth Brooks book signing.
你們穿這么土他們會信的
They'll believe you because of your clothes.
我要去找找洗手間
I'm gonna go look for the bathroom.
-好吧 -看 她這么緊張 真是可愛
- Okay. - Oh, look, she is so nervous, it's adorable.
你覺得有沒有辦法
Um, uh, do you think that there's any way
讓吉米的愛和莉莉打個招呼
we can get KimmyLoveandStuff to come over and meet Lily?
我不被允許看她的眼睛 所以不行
I'm not allowed to look her in the eye, so no.
我是羅納多
This is Ronaldo.
從地上撿起來 吹吹灰放回托盤里就好了
Just pick it up, blow on it, and put it back on the tray.
這種問題還用問
Are you kidding me with these questions?
我們得讓吉米的愛
We got to get KimmyLoveandStuff
跟莉莉打個招呼
to say hi to Lily.
她的狗波在那兒 她應該在附近
Well, there's her dog, Boo, so she's nearby.
我想到一個簡單的好主意
Okay, I just got a really sketchy but great idea.
你帶肉干了嗎
Um, did you pack your jerky?
火雞 牛肉 還是三文魚
Turkey, beef, or salmon?
-我們要這么干 -拜托
- Here's what we're gonna do. - Oh, please.
這又不是我第一次用包包里的肉干
This is not the first time I've lured an animal
把小動物從它主人身邊引開了
away from its owner with my purse jerky.
波 過來 波 想吃點好吃的嗎
Boo, come here. Boo, you want some treats?
好女孩 過來
Good girl. Come here.
讓開 波
Move! Boo!
有人看到波了嗎
Does anyone have eyes on Boo?!
那兩個老男人搶走她了
Those old men snatched her.
你們是想偷走我的狗嗎
Are you trying to steal my dog?
不不不 不好意思 我們只是想
No, no, no, no. I'm so sorry. We were just --
我們只是想吸引你的注意
We're just trying to, uh, get your attention.
是這樣的 我們的女兒 莉莉
Yeah, you see, our daughter, Lily, she --
她是你的超級粉絲
she's a massive fan
她現在有點沮喪 我們只是
and she's a little depressed right now and we just --
我們想再次看到她的笑臉
we want to see her smile again.
我的天
Oh...my...God.
同志爸爸最好了
Gay dads are the best!
-我們也是這么說的 -我們說的
- That's what we said. - We say that.
我覺得因為我們喜歡找樂子
I think it's because we love to have fun,
而且又不害怕面對現實
but we're also not afraid to get real.
我不想看到你們的女兒不高興
Aww. I hate the idea of your daughter not smiling.
讓我們給她帶來快樂吧
Let's go make her day.
好 那邊的是她
Okay, well, that's her right there.
那是莉莉
Um, that's Lily.
拍下來
Film this.
她在跟我說話嗎
I-Is she talking to me?
是的
Yeah.
當然 吉米的愛小姐
Of course, Ms. LoveandStuff.
你們好 粉絲們 這里是你們的吉米
Hey, lovers and stuffers. It's your girl, Kimmy.
我們現在在我的發布派對
We're here at my launch party
我要去給我的頭號粉絲一個驚喜
where I'm about to surprise my biggest fan.
你們準備好看某人的"吉"動反應了嗎
You ready to see someone's mind kim-plode?
你好 莉莉 你玩得開心又有愛嗎
Hey, Lily. You having fun and stuff?
你好
Hey.
莉莉 這是吉米的愛
Lily, it's KimmyLoveandStuff.
我知道 我說了"你好"
I know. I said "Hey."
你知道嗎 我覺得她是震驚得語無倫次
You know what? I think she's in shock.
莉莉 不如你給她講講你最喜歡的視頻
Lily, why don't you tell her your favorite video.
我的最愛是你講種族歧視
Mine was when you tackled racism
然后給自己綁了個可愛的魚尾辮
and gave yourself that cute fishtail braid.
是啊 該莉莉說了
Uh-huh. And Lily.
我已經不看你的視頻了 抱歉 我們能走嗎
I don't watch them anymore. Sorry. Can we go?
停 拿過來
Cut! Give me that!
莉莉 你這樣很不禮貌
Lily? You're -- You're being very rude.
超級不禮貌
Extra rude!
你們是誰 你們怎么進來的
And who are you people and how did you get in here?
-加斯·布魯克斯 -等我查清楚你們就完了
- Garth Brooks. - When I find out, heads will roll.
-感覺真是尷尬死人了 -你還尷尬 那我們呢
- I'm so embarrassed. - You're so embarrassed?
你們還好意思尷尬
You're so embarrassed?
好了 我們準備好給史黛拉做手術了
Okay. We're ready for Stella.
我還沒準備好
Well, I'm not ready.
杰 好了
Jay, come on.
好吧 小心點
All right. Careful.
等一下 我得和她說兩句話
Wait a second. I-I have to say something.
小姑娘 我知道你很害怕
Little girl, I know you're scared.
我也怕 但你是一個斗士
Me too. But you're a fighter.
"別擔心 爸爸 我會沒事的"
"Don't worry, Daddy. I'll be fine."
她的聲音不是這樣
She doesn't sound like that.
抱歉 她會很好的
Sorry. She'll do great.
你是怎么回事 我從沒見過你這樣
What is going on with you? I've never seen you like this.
我不知道
I don't know.
我十歲的時候 爸爸救了只狗帶回家
When I was 10, Dad came home with a rescue,
我興奮得不行
and I was so damned excited.
但那只狗根本不想理我
But the dog wanted nothing to do with me --
直奔向我妹妹 永遠只跟著我打轉
went straight to my sister and never left her side.
數年后 我們養的小狗也只粘著迪迪
Then years later, we got a puppy who went right to Dede,
我一接近她就沖我咆哮
growled at me every time I went near her.
但我什么努力都沒做 斯黛拉就選了我
But with Stella, I didn't even bother trying, and she chose me.
而我或許再也見不到她了
Now I may never see her again.
我坐不住 我得出去走走
I-I-I can't sit here. I need to take a walk.
做哪種手術
What kind of surgery?
不過是調整一下呼吸問題
They just have to fix her breathing.
沒什么大不了的
It's not a big deal.
他們是這么告訴你的嗎
Is that what they told you?
我要是你就會更上心
I'd be careful if I were you.
這話什么意思
What do you mean?
男人對寵物的愛很瘋狂
Men get crazy about their animals.
我丈夫以前有只丑貓 脖子上有個大瘤
My husband had this horrible cat with a big lump on its neck.
是良性的 我丈夫不介意
It was benign, didn't bother my husband,
但我一看到就鬧心
but I couldn't stand looking at it.
于是某天 我丈夫上班后
So one day, when my husband was at work,
我帶貓來這 讓他們把瘤切了
I brought the cat in here to have them take that thing off
然后
and --
它死在了手術臺上
It died right on the table.
不 你丈夫發火了嗎
Ay, no. Was your husband mad?
發火了 已經是前夫了
Ex-husband, so yeah.
媽的
Damn it.
你好
Hola.
有人嗎
Hello?
這下好了 我還以為下一個是我
Well, all righty. I thought I was next.
我還是第一次在看房時慢烤肋排
Well, that's the first time I've slow-cooked ribs for a showing.
是我媽的菜譜
Mother's recipe.
你準備好出價了嗎
So, are you ready to make an offer?
我說不好 菲爾
I don't know, Phil.
哪里說不好 阿嬌
Don't know what, Pep?
我就是沒感覺
I'm just not feeling it.
或許我們該再看看別的房子
Maybe we should see some more houses?
沒問題
No problemo.
你想看其他社區的房子
Um, did you want to look in another neighborhood
還是想留在地獄里
or stay right here in Hell?!
你說什么
I beg your --
我說求求你 老天爺 買這房子吧
No, I beg. For God's sakes, buy this house.
我整個職業生涯里從沒這么賣力過
I've worked harder for you than any client in my entire career.
我不知道你是優柔寡斷
I don't know if you're indecisive,
虐待狂 還是單純的精神病
sadistic, or just plain crazy.
親愛的
Hey there, honey.
你還在看房 對不對
You're still there, aren't you?
他差兩筆就簽好了
He's just dotting the I's, crossing the T's.
還在耍你 別理他了
Yanking your chain. Dump him.
比爾隨時會到
Listen, Bill's about to be here any minute,
情況有變
and the situation has changed.
我得掛了
Got to go.
回來 我照你吩咐找到廁所有錦鯉池的房呢
Get back here! I found you a bathroom with a koi pond!
斯黛拉在車上 上車
I have Stella! Get in!
她在哪
Where is she?
-在后面 -她還好嗎
- She's in the back. - Is she okay?
我把她劫出來的 我不能逼你這么做
I busted her out. I can't make you do this.
假如她有什么三長兩短
If something happens to her,
你永遠不會原諒我
you're never going to forgive me,
我不想像這樣失去你
and I don't want to lose you like that.
真感人 但你沒在停車標志下停車
Well, that's touching, but you just blew through a stop sign.
她在寵物醫院或許更安全些
She'd probably be safer at the vet.
羅納多 是我 菲爾·鄧菲
Ronaldo. It's Phil Dunphy.
你好 菲爾
Hello, Phil.
我正在給天后備餐
I'm preparing a plate for a diva.
一切還好嗎
Is everything okay?
其實不太好
Uh, actually, no.
我對胡嬌發脾氣了
I lost my temper with Pepper
因為他告訴我還想再看別的房子
when he told me he wanted to see more houses,
我一直在給他打電話想道歉 可是
and I've been calling to apologize, but...
-他不接 -你怎么知道
- He's not picking up. - How did you know?
下半句還有可能是別的嗎
It seemed the only possible conclusion to your sentence.
菲爾 你知道為什么
Phil, do you know the reason
我不再跟胡嬌一起看房子了嗎
I stopped house hunting with Pepper?
是因為那次賣家以為胡嬌是你爺爺嗎
Was it when that seller thought Pepper was your grandpa?
從那以后他就不準我涂防曬霜了
He hasn't let me wear sunscreen since.
不 因為我終于意識到他是不會買房的
No. I finally realized he wasn't going to buy a house.
你開玩笑嗎 我浪費了數百個小時
Are you kidding? I've wasted hundreds of hours.
我疝氣手術都延期了 他為什么這樣對我
I postponed hernia surgery. Why would he do that to me?
他喜歡你
He likes you.
大多數直男都覺得胡嬌很煩人
Most straight guys find Pepper annoying,
可你總對他那么友好
but you're always so nice with him.
我想他是擔心假如買了房
I think he's afraid if he buys a house,
-就再也見不到你了 -真的嗎
- he'll never see you again. - Really?
一直這么憋著實在太痛苦了
Wow, it's so painful keeping everything inside.
他就是這么長大的
It's how he was raised.
不 是我的疝帶不管用了
No, my truss isn't working.
我得趕快安排動手術
I've got to schedule that procedure.
你知道胡嬌在哪嗎
Do you know where Pepper is?
他每次難過都去一個特別的地方
He has a special place he goes when he's sad.
挺基的 你看過《愛樂之城》嗎
It's pretty gay. Have you ever seen the movie "La La Land"?
當然 等等 是不是能眺望城市的長椅
Of course. Wait, does he go to the bench overlooking the city
就是瑞恩·高斯林和艾瑪·斯通
where Ryan Gosling and Emma Stone
跳著踢踏舞愛上彼此的地方
tap danced into each other's hearts?
-沒有很基啊 -好吧
- That's not so gay. - Okay.
不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
拜托你把耳機摘下來
Take those things off, please.
我們現在得談談你到底是怎么回事
We need to talk about whatever's going on with you right now.
-我沒事 -不 你有事
- I'm fine. - No, you're not fine.
你悶悶不樂又冷漠疏遠
You're sullen and aloof and --
你讓我們丟人 當著吉米...
and you embarrassed us in front of KimmyLoveandStu --
我說不下去了
I can't say it again. I can't.
我們給了你每個少女夢想中的一天
Okay, we gave you every tween girl's dream day,
而你笑都沒笑一下
and-and you can barely crack a smile.
這不是我夢想中的一天 是你們的
It's not my dream day. It's yours.
我沒有你們這種少女心
I'm not the same kind of tween girl you guys are.
可我們喜歡一樣的東西
But we love all the same things.
我變了 我不喜歡碧昂絲
I've changed. I don't like Beyonce.
你把這話收回去
You take that back!
或小甜甜
Or Britney.
或嘎嘎
Or Gaga.
我只是因為你們喜歡而假裝喜歡
I only fake it 'cause you guys like that stuff.
我和你們不一樣
I'm different.
寶貝 這就是你低落的原因嗎
Well, honey, is it -- is that why you've been feeling so down,
因為你覺得你和我們不一樣
because you-you feel different than us?
不知道 我好像覺得和很多人都不一樣
I don't know. I guess I feel different than a lot of people.
寶貝 這點你兩個爸太有共鳴了
Well, sweetie, that is one thing your dad and I can relate to.
我想這才是有一對同志老爸最棒的地方
I guess, well, that's the great thing about having two gay dads.
我們知道不合群是什么感覺
We-we know what it feels like to be an outsider.
慢慢就好了
Okay, but here's what happens.
你會找到像你一樣不合群的人
You start finding people who don't quite fit in,
你們一起結伴不合群
and you start not fitting in together.
我們永遠不想讓你覺得
We never want you to feel like
你在我們面前得裝成其他人
you have to be someone else for us.
-永遠 -說回來
- Never. - I mean --
你總聽的是什么音樂
What is this music you're always listening to?
-快 讓我們也聽聽 -是啊
- Come on. Let us in. - Yeah.
好吧 我喜歡這種的
Okay. I like this.
來 放來聽聽吧
Okay. Let's put it on, huh?
好啦 準備好了
All right. Here we go.
? 你的理智在哪里 ?
♪ Where's your sanity? ♪
-有意思 -對啊
- Fun! - Yeah.
是啊 真的 我喜歡
Yeah, yeah, I like it.
她有一天一定會殺了我們
She's gonna kill us someday.
我想跟說 我真的很感激
Hey. I just want to say, I really appreciate you
你愿意費心救出斯黛拉
wanting to save Stella like that.
斯黛拉并不是唯一主動選你的人
Well, Stella is not the only one that choose you.
我也每天都選你 而且我比表面上更愛她
I choose you every day, and I love her more than I show.
好啦 小寶貝 我放你進家里
Okay, sweetheart. Let's get you inside.
我再給咱倆煎上牛排吃
I'll throw on a couple of steaks for both of us.
這是什么亂七八糟的狗
What the hell dog is this?
-是斯黛拉啊 -才不是
- It's Stella. - No, it's not.
都八年了 你還認不出咱家的狗嗎
Eight years, you don't recognize our dog?
都十年了 你還認不出我剪頭發了嗎
Well, 10 years, and you don't notice one haircut?
等我們回到獸醫那里 手術已經結束
By the time we got through to the vet, the surgery was over.
斯黛拉平安無恙
And Stella was fine.
我得承認歌洛莉亞這次真的勞心勞力
I just have to say Gloria really stepped up
協助我的寶貝身體康復
and nursed my baby back to health.
除了一個問題
Only one problem.
她現在選我了
Stella choose me now.
她不是真心的 是因為你給她止痛藥
It's not real. You give her pain meds.
她只是在當自己毒販的舔狗
It's like she's sucking up to her dealer.
你好啊 比爾
Hi, Bill.
-您好 -請進
- Hey. - Come on in.
-謝謝 -鄧菲先生在家嗎
- Thanks. - Is, uh, Mr. Dunphy around, too?
不在 但他應該在回家的路上了
Uh, no, he's probably on his way back,
我們有事應該等他回來了再說
and we should definitely wait for him.
可是我很快就得趕去上班了
Oh. I actually have to get to work pretty soon.
或許你代表一下你們倆發表意見吧
Do you think maybe you could just speak for the both of you?
不行 菲爾非常有主見
Nope. Phil is very opinionated.
也非常嚴格 "一切以我說了算"
And strict. "What I say goes around here."
他是個令人畏懼的顧客
He's a very scary customer.
好吧 我真得沒得選了
Okay. I don't really have a choice here.
鄧菲先生與太太
Mr. And Mrs. Dunphy...
你們愿意給像我這樣的人一個機會
would you be willing to take a chance on a guy like me
-然后讓我... -艾麗克斯現在結婚太早了
and let me -- Alex is too young to get married.
抱歉了 菲爾他這人暴脾氣
I'm sorry. Phil, who is very quick to anger,
絕對不會同意
would never allow it.
我不是要來提親啊
Oh, I wasn't asking to marry Alex.
這... 這是在干嘛
What -- What's happening?
然后更怪的事發生了
And then it got weirder.
女士們先生們
Ladies and gentlemen...
我向大家展示我的最新發明
...I give you my new invention,
專利的自我救贖鞋拉衣
the Pull-Yourself-Up-By-Your-Bootstraps™.
這種事情你碰過多少次了
How many times has this happened to you?
你在床上睡覺
You're in bed, asleep.
突然之間
All of a sudden...
天啊 糟糕
Oh, no.
地震了 沒時間穿好衣服
It's an earthquake. No time to get dressed.
你只能再次光著身子立刻逃到大街上
I'm gonna have to run out into the street naked again.
除非...
Huh. Unless...
那我就能一秒逃出家門啦
And I'm out the door in seconds.
-行啊 -就這樣嗎
- Oh, okay. - That's it?
你不是來我家提親的嗎
You didn't come to ask for my hand in marriage?
什... 當然不是啊
Wh-- Of course not.
"當然不是" 你這話什么意思
What do you mean, "Of course not"?
那我們交往干嘛 比爾
What are we doing, Bill?
寶貝 別得了便宜還賣乖
Honey, take the win.
冷靜 首先呢
Okay, first of all,
你是個智慧超群又獨立自主的女性
you're a super smart, independent woman
前方有大好的未來在等著你
with an amazing future ahead of you.
你怎么會想現在結婚呢
Why would you want to get married right now?
所以呢 那你說你昨天
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm. So, what were you doing
去珠寶行里做什么
in that jewelry store yesterday?
是去鐘表珠寶行里給手表換電池啊
I was getting a battery for my watch.
你怎么會知道我去鐘表珠寶行啊
How did you know I was in a jewelry store?
那你那條短信寫著...
And what about that text you s--
無論如何
For what it's worth,
如果我之前知道你有這意愿 我今天就求婚了
if that's what I thought you wanted, I would propose today.
我挺確定你就是我一生的某某
Hmm. I'm pretty sure you're my forever someone.
真的嗎
Really?
亞歷桑德拉·鄧菲
Alexandra Dunphy...
-你愿意... -媽
- would you... - Mom!
好了 大家平身 行了
Okay, everybody up. All right.
起來 很多事得處理 很多火得去滅呢
There we go. A lot of fires to put out.
下一次再問 我會把這句話說完
Next time, I'll get to the end.
下一次你問 我或許就準備好了
Next time, I might be ready.
我真不喜歡解放版的艾麗克斯
Ugh. Not a fan of liberated Alex.
美好的夜晚
Lovely night.
你來這里做什么
What are you doing here?
我打給你你愛人問你會上哪了
I called Ronaldo looking for you.
每當發現我人生不像音樂劇美好時 我都來這
I come to this place when life turns out not to be a musical.
而我常常來這里
I'm up here a lot.
我吼了你 對不起
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
菲爾 你也不是第一個
Well, Phil, you're not the first person
覺得我討人厭了
to find me a tad trying.
你聽了可能很驚訝 但其實我沒有多少朋友
This may shock you, but I don't have many friends.
表達點驚訝吧 菲爾
Express some shock, Phil.
但你有很多朋友啊
But you have tons of friends.
米奇爾與小卡都愛你
Mitch and Cam love you.
偶爾接觸的話他們還行
Yeah, they're okay in small doses.
但直男朋友就從不這樣了
And a straight-guy friend, never.
很多直男們覺得我...
A lot of straight guys find me...
-煩人嗎 -是太有威懾力
- Annoying? - Intimidating.
別亂接我的話 這又不是你比我猜
Wait for me to finish. This isn't Mad Libs.
但你不相信我喜歡你嗎 胡嬌
Don't you believe that I like you, though, Pepper?
我想相信啊 但或許我對你來說只是個累贅
I want to, but maybe I'm just a big, fat mother's purse to you.
我是你的朋友啊 胡椒
I'm your friend, Pepper
你干嘛啊
What are you doing?
這可是黃西裝
This is a yellow suit!
? 一生摯友 胡椒 ?
♪ Till the end, Pepper ♪
別弄得像戲精發戲癮
You're making a scene!
? 我聽過這陳腔濫調 ?
♪ I know that old line ♪
? 但只要我信了 你就會將我拋開 ?
♪ But as soon as I sign, he'll toss me aside like ♪
? 棄之敝履 ?
♪ Yesterday's wine ♪
? 我的真心日月可證 ?
♪ My heart's on my sleeve ♪
? 我想相信 ?
♪ I want to believe ♪
這也太尷尬了吧 我們是普通正常人
This is weird. We're people!
聽我說
Look.
你唯一能夠確定
The only way you're ever gonna find out
我們是不是朋友的方法就是買下房子
if we're friends is if you buy that house
然后看我會不會賺到好處就走人
and see if I stick around.
感覺是個好昂貴的實驗啊
Seems like an expensive experiment.
如果你真心喜歡那房子 就簽了報價單
Sign the offer... if you love the house.
簽字或者炒我
Either that or fire me.
你是你唯一能夠確認的辦法了
It's the only way you're gonna know.
-我的心就交給... -有緣再會啦
- My heart is in your... - I'll see you.
我就知道 你是無情的感情殺手
I knew it. Assassin!
我跟你鬧著玩呢
I'm messing with you.
我跟朋友們就喜歡鬧著玩
That's what I do with my friends.
懂了 真有意思
Oh. I see. Delightful.
我對直男的討喜方式還是菜鳥
I'm new at straight chummery.
別一直看你手表了 菲爾
Stop checking your watch, Phil.
糟糕
Oh, no!
是大地震
It's the big one!
我衣不蔽體
And I'm not dressed!
拿上地震逃生包
Grab the earthquake kit!
大家快躲到桌子底下
Everybody, get under a table!
冰箱里有現金
There's cash in the freezer!
老婆 這東西我們必需得投資啊
Honey, we gotta get in on this.
我高中男友當年從我家逃跑時也用得上
My highschool boyfirend could've used that.
都被你一句話毀了啦
You ruined it.